RG 062:165, Town of Windsor Locks
Connecticut State Library
Town of Windsor Locks records
1854-1941
Connecticut State Library
Windsor Locks (Conn.)
16.5 cubic feet
Administrative, election, court, land, school and tax records for the town of Windsor Locks.
RG062_165
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Windsor Locks was incorporated in May 1854 and was taken from Windsor.
Scope and Content
Administrative, election, court, land, school and tax records for the town of Windsor Locks.
Index Terms
Alternate Creators:
Connecticut. Justice of the Peace (Windsor Locks)
Subjects:
Public welfare -- Connecticut -- Windsor Locks; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Windsor Locks; Justices of the peace -- Connecticut -- Windsor Locks; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Windsor Locks -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Windsor Locks -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Windsor Locks -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Windsor Locks -- Registers
Places:
Windsor Locks (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1854-1941
  - T000653
    - Enrollment book, 1867-1869 (Box Box 1)
    - Index book, undated (Box Box 1)
    - Record of tramps housed, 1909-1910 (Box Box 1)
    - Grammar school register, 1866 (Box Box 1)
    - Justice Court records, 1860-1874 (Box Box 1)
    - Indexes to land records, undated (Box Box 1)
    - Lists of electors
      - 1857, 1858, 1860, 1861-1862, 1866-1868, 1868-1869, 1870-1871, 1872, 1873, 1874, 1875, 1876, 1877, 1878 (Box Box 2)
        There are two volumes each for the years 1860, 1873, 1875, 1876, 1878
      - 1879, 1880, 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884, 1885, 1886 (Box Box 3)
        There are two volumes each for the years 1879, 1881, 1882, 1883, 1886.
    - Cash book, 1854-1881; 1 volume
    - Daybook, 1854-1875; 1 volume
    - Ledger, 1854-1875; 1 volume
    - Individual tax lists
      These volumes are not boxed.
      - 1854, 1 volume
      - 1855, 1 volume
      - 1856, 1 volume
      - 1857, 1 volume
      - 1858, 1 volume
      - 1860, 1 volume
      - 1861, 1 volume
      - 1862, 1 volume
      - 1863, 1 volume
      - 1864, 1 volume
      - 1867, 1 volume
      - 1868, 1 volume
      - 1869, 1 volume
      - 1870, 1 volume
      - 1871, 1 volume
      - 1872, 1 volume
      - 1873, 1 volume
      - 1874, 1 volume
      - 1875, 1 volume
    - Tax abstracts
      - 1854, 1855, 1856, 1857, 1858, 1859, 1860, 1861 (Box Box 4)
      - 1864, 1865, 1866, 1867, 1868, 1869, 1870, 1871, 1872 (Box Box 5)
      - 1873, 1874, 1875, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879, 1880 (Box Box 6)
  - 1985-022
    - Town poor relief ledgers
      - 1933-1936, 1 volume
      - 1936-1938, 1 volume
      - 1939-1940, 1 volume
      - 1940-1941, 1 volume